Guide to the New World Writing Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Manuscripts, 1952-1959; Series II; 5.4; (13 boxes)
  - Cassill, R. V. (Ronald Verlin) "The Romanticizing of Dr. Fless", undated (Box 23, Folder 616)
  - Catlin, George. "Sketch of Chief Clermont", undated (Box 23, Folder 617)
  - Chang, Diana
    - "The Brilliant Nylon Balloons", undated (Box 23, Folder 618)
    - "The Eurasians", undated (Box 23, Folder 619)
  - Chaulot, Paul. "A Stranger", undated (Box 23, Folder 620)
  - Chen, Mei Yao. "A Friend Advises Me to Stop Drinking", undated (Box 23, Folder 621)
  - Chilver, Sally
    - "A Queen Match", undated (Box 23, Folder 622)
    - "From a Small Black Notebook, Property of the Accused", undated (Box 23, Folder 623)
    - "The Hopeless Case", undated (Box 23, Folder 624)
    - "The Poacher's Bitch", undated (Box 23, Folder 625)
    - "Spouses Parting", undated (Box 23, Folder 626)
  - Chubak, Sadeq. "The Baboon Whose Buffoon Was Dead", undated (Box 23, Folder 627)
  - Chumacero, Alí. "Green Eyes", undated (Box 23, Folder 628)
  - Clancy, Joseph P. "Adam's Children", undated (Box 24, Folder 629)
  - Clay, George R. "We're All Guests", undated (Box 24, Folder 630)
  - Coggeshall, Helen
    - "Far into the Rocks", undated (Box 24, Folder 631)
    - "In the Rude Ages", undated (Box 24, Folder 632)
  - Cogswell, Fred. "Lycanthropy", undated (Box 24, Folder 633)
  - Collins, Lucinda C. "The Conquest", undated (Box 24, Folder 634)
  - Connell, Evan S., Jr. "The Anatomy Lesson", undated (Box 24, Folder 635)
  - Cooke, Dorian. "In Memory of Dylan Thomas", undated (Box 24, Folder 636)
  - Cooper, Jane. "The Faithful", undated (Box 24, Folder 637)
  - Corke, Hilary. "In the Closing Fist of Evening", undated (Box 24, Folder 638)
  - Cortázar, Julio
    - "Flattening the Drops", undated (Box 24, Folder 639)
    - "The Lines of the Hand", undated (Box 24, Folder 640)
  - Coulette, Henri. "Catullus: 5", undated (Box 24, Folder 641)
  - Court, Artelia Bowne
    - "After A Jangling, Ram-Bum Argument", undated (Box 24, Folder 642)
    - "The Chair Was Stiff", undated (Box 24, Folder 643)
  - Cowley, Malcolm. "The Time of the Rhetoricians", undated (Box 24, Folder 644)
  - Cummings, E. E. (Edward Estlin) "Poem", undated (Box 24, Folder 645)
  - Curnow, Allen. "A Small Room with Large Windows", undated (Box 24, Folder 646)
  - Currie, Ellen. "Moses Supposes", undated (Box 24, Folder 647)
  - Dagerman, Stig. "Unpardonable", undated (Box 24, Folder 648)
  - Dante Alighieri. "The Purgatorio: Canto II", undated (Box 24, Folder 649)
  - De Andrade, Carlos Drummond
    - "Miguel and His Theft", undated (Box 24, Folder 650)
    - "Pilgrimage", undated (Box 24, Folder 651)
  - De Holanda, Aurelio Buarque. "Poem", undated (Box 24, Folder 652)
  - De Lima, Jorge
    - "Calabar", undated (Box 24, Folder 653)
    - "Fear", undated (Box 24, Folder 654)
  - Delius, Anthony. "The Thinker", undated (Box 24, Folder 655)
  - De Onís, Harriet "Five Brazilian Poets", undated (Box 24, Folder 656)
  - Del Río, Angel. "Lorca: Poet in New York", undated (Box 24, Folder 657)
  - Dempsey, David. "Valse Triste", undated (Box 24, Folder 658)
  - Denney, Revel. "September Lemonade", undated (Box 24, Folder 659)
  - Dennis, Alice. "The Death of Miss Emma K. Wood", undated (Box 24, Folder 660)
  - DeSantillana, Giorgio. "Space, Time, and Understanding", undated (Box 24, Folder 661)
  - De Uries, Hendrik, "I Was in My Earliest Years", undated (Box 24, Folder 662)
  - Diamond, Sidney A. "Creation in Hollywood", undated (Box 24, Folder 663)
  - D'Olive, Gene. "Papa Is So Medieval", undated (Box 24, Folder 664)
  - Drake, Carol Christopher. "Song", undated (Box 24, Folder 665)
  - Duffield, Edward D. (Edward Dickinson). "Spring Day at Miss Orientiere's School for Young Ladies", undated (Box 24, Folder 666)
  - Duke, Osborn. "Struttin With Some Barbecue", undated (Box 24, Folder 667)
  - Dull, Kenneth. "Corners", undated (Box 24, Folder 668)
  - Dumur, Guy. "Sacrifice", undated (Box 24, Folder 669)
  - Duncun, Harry. "Monodies", undated (Box 24, Folder 670)
  - Duodu, M. Cameron. "Tough Guy in Town", undated (Box 24, Folder 671)
  - Eastlake, William. "Back to Indian Country", undated (Box 24, Folder 672)
  - Eberhart, Richard
    - "Note on a Poem", undated (Box 24, Folder 673)
    - "Pleasures of the Morning", undated (Box 24, Folder 674)
    - "Society of Friends", undated (Box 24, Folder 675)
    - "The Visionary Farms", undated (Box 24, Folder 676)
  - Eich, Gunter. "Pigeons", undated (Box 24, Folder 677)
  - Ekelof, Gunnar. "Bal Des Petits Lits Blancs", undated (Box 24, Folder 678)
  - Eliot, Alexander
    - "Artists on Horseback", undated (Box 24, Folder 679)
    - "A Connoisseur in Love", undated (Box 24, Folder 680)
  - Eliot, George P. "To Run a Chicken", undated (Box 24, Folder 681)
  - Ellison, James Whitfield. "Jade the Greatest", undated (Box 24, Folder 682)
  - Ellison, Ralph
    - "A Coupla Scalped Indians", undated (Box 24, Folder 683)
    - "Did You Ever Dream Lucky?", undated (Box 24, Folder 684)
  - Elytis, Odysseus. "Poem", undated (Box 24, Folder 685)
  - Engel, Monroe. "A Matter of Reality", undated (Box 24, Folder 686)
  - Esekie, Bruno. "The Suit Case", undated (Box 24, Folder 687)
  - Evans, Oliver. "The Theme of Spiritual Isolation in Carson McCullers", undated (Box 24, Folder 688)
  - Farrell, James T. (James Thomas)
    - "Dr. Mencken: Criticus Americanus", undated (Box 25, Folder 689)
    - "On A Train To Rome", undated (Box 25, Folder 690)
  - Feibleman, Peter S. "In Between and Afterwards", undated (Box 25, Folder 691)
  - Fenton, Charles A. "Hemingway's Kansas City Apprenticeship", undated (Box 25, Folder 692)
  - Fenton, Charles A. "The Writer As Professor", undated (Box 25, Folder 693)
  - Fey, Isabella. "Some Contemporary Icelandic Poems", undated (Box 25, Folder 694)
  - Figueredo, Álvaro. "Naked", undated (Box 25, Folder 695)
  - Fitts, Dudley. "Eight Poems by Martial", undated (Box 25, Folder 696)
  - Florit, Eugenio. "Autumn", undated (Box 25, Folder 697)
  - Foote, Shelby. "Day of Battle", undated (Box 25, Folder 698)
  - Forni, Luigi. "Peace For Geretiello", undated (Box 25, Folder 699)
  - Franco, Afonso Arinos de Melo. "Robinson Crusoe", undated (Box 25, Folder 700)
  - Frankenberg, Lloyd. "Villa D'Este", undated (Box 25, Folder 701)
  - Fraser, G. S. "New British Poets", undated (Box 25, Folder 702)
  - Fremantle, Anne Jackson. "By Grace of Love", undated (Box 25, Folder 703)
  - Fremantle, Anne Jackson. "For Earth Too Hard", undated (Box 25, Folder 704)
  - Friedburg, Gertrude. "The Wayward Cravat", undated (Box 25, Folder 705)
  - Fuller, Roy. "Knole", undated (Box 25, Folder 706)
  - Fuyohiko, Kitagawa. "A Downpour", undated (Box 25, Folder 707)
  - Gaddis, William. "Le Chemin Des Anes", undated (Box 25, Folder 708)
  - Gallegos, Rómulo. "Peace in the Mountain", undated (Box 25, Folder 709)
  - Gardner, Isabella. "Lines to a Sea Green Lover", undated (Box 25, Folder 710)
  - Garrett, George. "The Wounded Soldier", undated (Box 25, Folder 711)
  - Garrigue, Jean
    - "The Animal Hotel", undated (Box 25, Folder 712)
    - "These Days So Calm and Perfect", undated (Box 25, Folder 713)
  - Genet, Jean. "The Thief's Journal", undated (Box 25, Folder 714)
  - Ghiselin, Brewster. "His Babylonian Heart", undated (Box 25, Folder 715)
  - Gide, André. "On Literary Influence", undated (Box 25, Folder 716)
  - Glanville, Brian. "Miss Lawrance Will Be at Home", undated (Box 25, Folder 717)
  - Glaze, Andrew. "Countess Katerina and the Duchess", undated (Box 25, Folder 718)
  - Gold, Herbert
    - "The Man Who Was Not With It", undated (Box 25, Folder 719)
    - "The Prospect Before Us", undated (Box 25, Folder 720)
  - Goldknopf, David. "The Case of Henry Swasey", undated (Box 25, Folder 721)
  - González, José Luis. "There's a Little Negro at the Bottom of the Cano", undated (Box 25, Folder 722)
  - Goodwin, John. "The Visitation", undated (Box 25, Folder 723)
  - Granat, Robert
    - "My Apples", undated (Box 25, Folder 724)
    - "The Sigh", undated (Box 25, Folder 725)
  - Granell, Eugenio Fernández. Drawings., undated (Box 25, Folder 726)
  - Grau, Shirley Ann. "Isle Aux Chiens", undated (Box 25, Folder 727)
  - Graves, Robert. "Seven Poets", undated (Box 25, Folder 728)
  - Gregor, Arthur. "Inheriting a Secret", undated (Box 26, Folder 729)
  - Gregory, Horace
    - "Amy Lowell: The London Adventures", undated (Box 26, Folder 730)
    - "The Chinese Garden", undated (Box 26, Folder 731)
    - "H. G. Wells: A Wreath for the Liberal Tradition", undated (Box 26, Folder 732)
    - "James T. Farrell: Beyond the Province of Art", undated (Box 26, Folder 733)
    - "Poet Without Critics: A Note on Robinson Jeffers", undated (Box 26, Folder 734)
  - Griffin, C. W. "The Anatomy of Sainthood", undated (Box 26, Folder 735)
  - Griffin, John Howard
    - "Chez Durand", undated (Box 26, Folder 736)
    - "Sauce for the Gander", undated (Box 26, Folder 737)
    - "Taos", undated (Box 26, Folder 738)
  - Grímsson, Stefán Horður. "The Car at the Clearing", undated (Box 26, Folder 739)
  - Gudmundsson, Thomas. "The Great Caravan", undated (Box 26, Folder 740)
  - Guérard, Albert J. (Albert Joseph). "The Ivory Tower and the Dust Bowl", undated (Box 26, Folder 741)
  - Guillen, Jorge. "Federico in Person", undated (Box 26, Folder 742)
  - Gunn, Thom. "Light Sleeping", undated (Box 26, Folder 743)
  - Hall, Carol
    - "Chorus from the Woodcutter's House (IV-1)", undated (Box 26, Folder 744)
    - "Sermon", undated (Box 26, Folder 745)
  - Hall, Donald
    - "Apology", undated (Box 26, Folder 746)
    - "Like a Man, Shining", undated (Box 26, Folder 747)
    - "The New Poetry", undated (Box 26, Folder 748)
  - Hall, J. C.
    - "The Burning Hare", undated (Box 26, Folder 749)
    - "The Playground by the Church", undated (Box 26, Folder 750)
  - Hamburger, Michael
    - "Nine Modern German Poets", undated (Box 26, Folder 751)
    - "Travellers", undated (Box 26, Folder 752)
  - Hamilton, Horace E. "Album", undated (Box 26, Folder 753)
  - Hansen, Martin Alfred. "Harvest Feast", undated (Box 26, Folder 754)
  - Hards, Terence
    - "How It Was", undated (Box 26, Folder 755)
    - "Impossible Coast", undated (Box 26, Folder 756)
    - "A Picture", undated (Box 26, Folder 757)
    - "To Meet Again", undated (Box 26, Folder 758)
  - Hartley, Anthony. "The King's Evil", undated (Box 26, Folder 759)
  - Hasegawa, Sabro. "Five Calligraphic Drawings", undated (Box 26, Folder 760)
  - Hazo, Samuel J.
    - "Battle Burial", undated (Box 26, Folder 761)
    - "Lull", undated (Box 26, Folder 762)
    - "Parachutist", undated (Box 26, Folder 763)
  - Hecht, Roger. "Aaron Burr: (1756-1836)", undated (Box 26, Folder 764)
  - Heller, Joseph. "Catch-18", undated (Box 26, Folder 765)
  - Hemley, Cecil. "The New and Experimental", undated (Box 26, Folder 766)
  - Herman, Bonnie. "A Song of Christopher", undated (Box 26, Folder 767)
  - Hershberger, Ruth. "Barn and Seasons", undated (Box 26, Folder 768)
  - Herzig, Albert. "The Footprint", undated (Box 26, Folder 769)
  - Hewitt, John. "Shadow and Stone", undated (Box 26, Folder 770)
  - Hitchcock, Henry-Russell and Johnson, Phillip C. "The Buildings We See", undated (Box 26, Folder 771)
  - Hochman, Sandra. "Silence", undated (Box 27, Folder 772)
  - Hoetis, Themistocles. "Akin and the Small Boy", undated (Box 27, Folder 773)
  - Hoffman, Daniel G.
    - "The Everlasting", undated (Box 27, Folder 774)
    - "Islands", undated (Box 27, Folder 775)
    - "That the Pear Delights Me Now", undated (Box 27, Folder 776)
  - Holmes, John. "Hummingbird and Seagull", undated (Box 27, Folder 777)
  - Howes, Barbara. "Tea in the Garden", undated (Box 27, Folder 778)
  - Humphries, Rolfe
    - "A Brecon Version", undated (Box 27, Folder 779)
    - "Translation in Revival", undated (Box 27, Folder 780)
  - Hunter, Sam. "Jackson Pollack: The Maze and the Minotaur", undated (Box 27, Folder 781)
  - Hutchins, Patricia
    - "Ezra Pound in Kensington", undated (Box 27, Folder 782)
    - "James Joyce on Holiday", undated (Box 27, Folder 783)
  - Hudson, Patricia E. "Rosemary", undated (Box 27, Folder 784)
  - Hyun, P. P.
    - "Seven Modern Korean Poets", undated (Box 27, Folder 785)
    - "Spirit Burned", undated (Box 27, Folder 786)
  - Idan, Lionel K. "It's Ritual Murder", undated (Box 27, Folder 787)
  - Ignaton, David. "Each Night", undated (Box 27, Folder 788)
  - Inoue, Mitsuko. "Minerva's Whispering", undated (Box 27, Folder 789)
  - Insu, Lee. "Morning Prayer in the Desert", undated (Box 27, Folder 790)
  - Ionesco, Eugène. "The Bald Soprano", undated (Box 27, Folder 791)
  - Ish, David Allen. "The Fantasy People", undated (Box 27, Folder 792)
  - Isherwood, Christopher. "The World in the Evening", undated (Box 27, Folder 793)
  - Jackson, James Turner. "The Visit", undated (Box 27, Folder 794)
  - Jackson, Shirley. "The Lovely House", undated (Box 27, Folder 795)
  - Jayakar, Pupul. "The Girl and the Dark Goddess", undated (Box 27, Folder 796)
  - Jeffers, Robinson
    - "Animula", undated (Box 27, Folder 797)
    - "The Shears", undated (Box 27, Folder 798)
  - Jennings, Elizabeth. "Fisherman in the Arno", undated (Box 27, Folder 799)
  - Johannessen, Matthias. "A Black She-Cat", undated (Box 27, Folder 800)
  - Jones, Howard Mumford. "A Little Learning", undated (Box 27, Folder 801)
  - Jones, James
    - "A Bottle of Cream", undated (Box 27, Folder 802)
    - "None Sing So Wildly", undated (Box 27, Folder 803)
  - Josephs, Lawrence
    - "Poem", undated (Box 27, Folder 804)
    - "Two Children at Watch Hill", undated (Box 27, Folder 805)
  - Junior, Raimundo Magalhaes. "The Promised Land", undated (Box 27, Folder 806)
  - Justice, Donald. "A Winter Ode to the Old Men of Lummus Park, Miami, Florida", undated (Box 27, Folder 807)
  - Kadish, Mortimer R. (Mortimer Raymond) "Anthem for French Horn", undated (Box 27, Folder 808)
  - Katue, Kitasono
    - "Eight Contemporary Japanese Poets", undated (Box 27, Folder 809)
    - "Moonlight Night in a Bag", undated (Box 27, Folder 810)
  - Kay, Ellen. "Charity Clinic", undated (Box 27, Folder 811)
  - Kazantzakis, Nikos. "The Odyssey", undated (Box 27, Folder 812)
  - Kerouac, Jack
    - "Jazz Excerpts", undated (Box 27, Folder 813)
    - "Jazz of the Beat Generation", undated (Box 27, Folder 814)
  - King, Joy Lee. "Satiety", undated (Box 27, Folder 815)
  - Kinnell, Galway. "First Song", undated (Box 27, Folder 816)
  - Kinnell, Galway. "The Permanence of Love", undated (Box 27, Folder 817)
  - Ki Rim, Kim. "The Butterfly and the Sea", undated (Box 27, Folder 818)
  - Kirsch, Robert. "Do Not Go Gentle", undated (Box 27, Folder 819)
  - Kizu, Toyotaro. "Poem", undated (Box 27, Folder 820)
  - Knobil, Henry. "A Little Death Is Gentle", undated (Box 27, Folder 821)
  - Kolmar, Gertrud. "The Unicorn", undated (Box 28, Folder 822)
  - Koningsberger, Hans. "Nine Modern Dutch Poems", undated (Box 28, Folder 823)
  - Krleza, Miroslav. "Hut Five B", undated (Box 28, Folder 824)
  - Kunitz, Stanley. "The Thing that Eats the Heart", undated (Box 28, Folder 825)
  - Kurt, Kim. "Spruce", undated (Box 28, Folder 826)
  - Kwangsu, Lee. "Longing for My Friends", undated (Box 28, Folder 827)
  - Kwangsu, Kim. "Individuality", undated (Box 28, Folder 828)
  - Ladd, Gabrielle. "Mathis Der Maler", undated (Box 28, Folder 829)
  - La Follette, Melvin Walker
    - "Angulus Ridet", undated (Box 28, Folder 830)
    - "Somnet Sequence", undated (Box 28, Folder 831)
    - "Summerhouse", undated (Box 28, Folder 832)
  - Lall, Arthur S. (Arthur Samuel)
    - "The House at Adampur", undated (Box 28, Folder 833)
    - "Tiger, Tiger", undated (Box 28, Folder 834)
  - Langer, Suzanne. "Art: The Symbol of Sentience", undated (Box 28, Folder 835)
  - Langland, Joseph
    - "The Amalfi Grotto", undated (Box 28, Folder 836)
    - "A Bestiary for Easter", undated (Box 28, Folder 837)
  - Larkin, Philip. "Mr. Bleaney", undated (Box 28, Folder 838)
  - Laughlin, Clarence John. "Inner Vision in Photography", undated (Box 28, Folder 839)
  - Laughlin, James. "The Egotron", undated (Box 28, Folder 840)
  - Lawner, Lynne. "If He Stroke My Cheek", undated (Box 28, Folder 841)
  - Lax, Robert. "The Circus", undated (Box 28, Folder 842)
  - Layzer, Robert B.
    - "Elegy", undated (Box 28, Folder 843)
    - "The Lawn Roller", undated (Box 28, Folder 844)
  - Lee, Alwyn. "Henry Miller - The Pathology of Isolation", undated (Box 28, Folder 845)
  - Lehman, John
    - "More Pages from an Auto Biography", undated (Box 28, Folder 846)
    - "New Soundings", undated (Box 28, Folder 847)
    - "Pages from an Autobiography", undated (Box 28, Folder 848)
  - Lehmann, Wilhelm. "February Moon", undated (Box 28, Folder 849)
  - Levine, Rosalind. "The Pomegranate", undated (Box 28, Folder 850)
  - Leyda, Jay. "Miss Emily's Maggie", undated (Box 28, Folder 851)
  - Leydenfrost, Robert J. "Man and Beast", undated (Box 28, Folder 852)
  - Lindergren, Erik. "Sonnet XXVII", undated (Box 28, Folder 853)
  - Locke, Alain. "The Negro in American Literature", undated (Box 28, Folder 854)
  - Lodeizen, Hans. "For Father", undated (Box 28, Folder 855)
  - Loerke, Oskar. "The Stone Path", undated (Box 28, Folder 856)
  - Logan, John
    - "The Lives of the Poet", undated (Box 28, Folder 857)
    - "The Picture for the Publisher", undated (Box 28, Folder 858)
  - Loos, André L. "Dana is a Thief", undated (Box 28, Folder 859)
  - Lorca, Federico García
    - Drawings, undated (Box 28, Folder 860)
    - "The Tragicomedy of a Don Cristobita and Dona Rosita", undated (Box 28, Folder 861)
  - Lowry, Malcolm. "Strange Comfort Afforded by the Profession", undated (Box 28, Folder 862)
  - Lucebert. "Harvest", undated (Box 28, Folder 863)
  - Lundkvist, Artur. "Caryatid", undated (Box 28, Folder 864)
  - Lynds, Dennis. "Yellow Gal", undated (Box 28, Folder 865)
  - Macauley, Robie. "The End of Pity", undated (Box 28, Folder 866)
  - McCallister, Claire. "A Day in the Country", undated (Box 28, Folder 867)
  - MacDonagh, Donagh. "Happy as Larry", undated (Box 28, Folder 868)
  - MacInnes, Maivi. "Running in the Park", undated (Box 28, Folder 869)
  - Madge, Charles. "The Tree of Life", undated (Box 29, Folder 870)
  - Magnússon, Sigurður A. "Betrayal", undated (Box 29, Folder 871)
  - Mailer, Norman. "The Paper House", undated (Box 29, Folder 872)
  - Makal, Mahmut. "Our Village", undated (Box 29, Folder 873)
  - Manoll, Michel. "A Sea Chant for Dylan Thomas", undated (Box 29, Folder 874)
  - Marberry, M. Marion. "Buffalo Bill Was a Great Man", undated (Box 29, Folder 875)
  - Marcus, David. "The Religion of Love", undated (Box 29, Folder 876)
  - Martinson, Harry. "Horse and Rider", undated (Box 29, Folder 877)
  - Matchett, William H.
    - "Packing a Photograph from Firenze", undated (Box 29, Folder 878)
    - "The Seafarer", undated (Box 29, Folder 879)
  - Matson, Peter. "The Funeral of Summer", undated (Box 29, Folder 880)
  - Matthews, T. S. (Thomas Stanley)
    - "Buried Alive", undated (Box 29, Folder 881)
    - "The Gate Marked Private", undated (Box 29, Folder 882)
    - "The Spy", undated (Box 29, Folder 883)
  - Matthiessen, Peter. "Late in the Season", undated (Box 29, Folder 884)
  - Mayhall, Jane. "Desire Rises", undated (Box 29, Folder 885)
  - Mead, Margaret. "Sex and Censorship in Contemporary Society", undated (Box 29, Folder 886)
  - Meldon, Maurice. "Purple Path to the Poppy Fields", undated (Box 29, Folder 887)
  - Menemancioglu, Nermin. "A Voice from Anatolia", undated (Box 29, Folder 888)
  - Mensah, Albert Kayper. "The Perfect Understander", undated (Box 29, Folder 889)
  - Merrill, James. "The Wintering Weeds", undated (Box 29, Folder 890)
  - Merton, Thomas. "Sports Without Blood", undated (Box 29, Folder 891)
  - Merwin, W. S. (William Stanley)
    - "Favor Island", undated (Box 29, Folder 892)
    - "The Wakening", undated (Box 29, Folder 893)
  - Michaux, Henri. "Experiment Five", undated (Box 29, Folder 894)
  - Miller, Vassar. "The Common Core", undated (Box 29, Folder 895)
  - Moffett, James
    - "The Man Behind", undated (Box 29, Folder 896)
    - "The Suicides of Private Greaves", undated (Box 29, Folder 897)
  - Montgomery, Marion. "Aunt Amma, Uncle Al: A Short History of the South", undated (Box 29, Folder 898)
  - Montgomery, Niall. "No Symbols Where none Intended", undated (Box 29, Folder 899)
  - Montale, Eugenio. "The House of the Customs Men", undated (Box 29, Folder 900)
  - Moore, Geoffrey
    - "American Prose Today", undated (Box 29, Folder 901)
    - "British Commonwealth Poets", undated (Box 29, Folder 902)
  - Moore, Nicholas. "Winter to Spring", undated (Box 29, Folder 903)
  - Moore, Rosalie
    - "Fabliaux for a Far-Flung Baby", undated (Box 29, Folder 904)
    - "Of Flying, Moths and Machines", undated (Box 29, Folder 905)
  - Moravia, Alberto. "Consuelo", undated (Box 30, Folder 906)
  - Morrien, Adriaan. "A Girl", undated (Box 30, Folder 907)
  - Morris, Herber
    - "Suns", undated (Box 30, Folder 908)
    - "That Speech", undated (Box 30, Folder 909)
  - Morris, Wright
    - "The Ability to Function", undated (Box 30, Folder 910)
    - "The Rites of Spring", undated (Box 30, Folder 911)
  - Morrison, Julia Maria. "Megalopolitan Room", undated (Box 30, Folder 912)
  - Moss, Howard
    - "The Skiers", undated (Box 30, Folder 913)
    - "Venice", undated (Box 30, Folder 914)
  - Murena, H.A. "The Center of Hell", undated (Box 30, Folder 915)
  - Myrivilis, Stratis. "The Goblins", undated (Box 30, Folder 916)
  - Nemerov, Howard
    - "The Goose Fish", undated (Box 30, Folder 917)
    - "Mousemeal", undated (Box 30, Folder 918)
    - "Mrs. Mandrill", undated (Box 30, Folder 919)
  - Neruda, Pablo. "Ode to Laziness", undated (Box 30, Folder 920)
  - Niedelman, R. F. "Alex's Fun: Well Boiled", undated (Box 30, Folder 921)
  - Nijihoff, Martinus. "The Song of the Foolish Bees", undated (Box 30, Folder 922)
  - Nims, John Frederick. "A Frieze of Cupids", undated (Box 30, Folder 923)
  - Nketia, J. H. Kwabena
    - "The Poetry of Drums", undated (Box 30, Folder 924)
    - "Voices of Ghana", undated (Box 30, Folder 925)
  - Norse, Harold. "Almonds Like Pink Snow", undated (Box 30, Folder 926)
  - Ocampo, Silvina. "The Infinite Horses", undated (Box 30, Folder 927)
  - Oakes, Philip
    - "The Ballad of Captain May", undated (Box 30, Folder 928)
    - "Love in Hunger", undated (Box 30, Folder 929)
  - O'Connor, Flannery
    - "Enoch and the Gorilla", undated (Box 30, Folder 930)
    - "You Can't Be Any Poorer Than Dead", undated (Box 30, Folder 931)
  - Odio, Eunice. Fragments from "Transit of Fire", undated (Box 30, Folder 932)
  - O'Faoláin, Seán.
    - "Childybawn", undated (Box 30, Folder 933)
    - "Narcissa and Lucifer", undated (Box 30, Folder 934)
  - O'Hara, Frank. "Poem", undated (Box 30, Folder 935)
  - Oliver, William. "Federico Garcia Lorca", undated (Box 30, Folder 936)
  - Olyosha, Yuri. "Liumpa", undated (Box 30, Folder 937)
  - Opoku, Andrew Amankua. "Afram", undated (Box 30, Folder 938)
  - Ortese, Anna Maria. "Family Scene", undated (Box 30, Folder 939)
  - Osaragi, Jiro. "The Garden of Groves and Ponds", undated (Box 30, Folder 940)
  - Osborn, Robert Chesley. Drawings., undated (Box 30, Folder 941)
  - Óskar, Jón. "The Sheep Roundup", undated (Box 30, Folder 942)
  - Otoo, Samuel K. "A Fisherman's Day", undated (Box 30, Folder 943)
  - Park, Robert. "In the Waking of My Eyes", undated (Box 30, Folder 944)
  - Palmer, Winthrop
    - "Bodies of Thirst", undated (Box 30, Folder 945)
    - "Modern Dance - Divertissement into Art", undated (Box 30, Folder 946)
  - Papatzonis, Takis. "The Sluggish of Mind", undated (Box 30, Folder 947)
  - Parkes, Frank E. K. "African Heaven", undated (Box 30, Folder 948)
  - Parra, Nicanor. "Piano Solo", undated (Box 30, Folder 949)